还是有些不错的男人的
There were some nice guys there.
但他们太沉默了
But they're all so quiet.
笑容尴尬 手心冒汗
Awkward smiles and sweaty palms.
我也没期待在这里见到像布拉德·皮特
I'm not expecting brad pitt/to walk into st. Theresa's.
只要有个能逗我笑 笑容温暖
Just someone who makes/me laugh.Has a nice smile.
头发浓密的就行了
Full head of hair.
你知道
You know,
像你这样的 Franklin先生
someone like you,mr. Franklin.
真可惜他们打算火化你
It's a shame they're/going to cremate you.
有什么需要吗?
can I help you?
Martin!
我的钱包就在那 拿走吧
My purse is right there.Go ahead.
要什么都拿去
Take whatever you want.
啊!
ah!
Irene 你叫我?
Irene? You call me?
Irene?
Irene!
你还好吗?
How're you doing?
很好
I'm fine.
要是你想知道...
Fyi...
依我看 男队犯的错比你更大
If you ask me,it's more/the guys' fault than yours.
House也有错
And house isn't blameless either.
- 要不是他让我们比赛.../- 是我的错
- If he hadn't pitted us all against each other.../- It was my fault.
我的失误
My mistake.
以前有这电话吗?
Was that always there?
喂
Hello.
好
Sure.
是House
It's house.
早上好 查理的天使们
Good morning,angels.
看到病历表 有个个案很有趣
As you will see from the file,we/have quite the interesting case.
不常有病人声称看得见死人吧
Not often do you get a/patient who sees dead people.
什么病历表?
What file?
搞什么鬼?
What the hell?
我半小时前就交给Bosley了/(霹雳娇娃中的重要角色)
I gave it to bosley a half hour ago.
没有半小时 才10分钟而已
It was not a half/hour.It was ten minutes.
他先去复印了急诊室记录
And he made copies of/the er records first.
少贫嘴 多奶油
Less lip,more whip.
我之所以接这个案例
I only agreed to take this case
是因为你说给我加奶油的摩卡咖啡
because you said that this mocha/frapalicious would have whip on it.
好 那我推荐给Foreman
Fine. I'll refer the case to foreman.
不行 慈爱医院解雇了他
Can't. Mercy fired him.
- 给我/- 他被解雇了?
- Gimme./- He got fired?
他在火线上抗命
He disobeyed a superior/officer under fire.
- 没被就地正法算好运了/- 你怎么知道的? 一直追踪他的信息?
- He's lucky he wasn't executed./- How do you know about it?You keeping tabs on him?
八卦八来的
Girls talk.
当Bosley蹒跚而来...
When bosley drags his/ancient ass in there...
我来了
I'm here.
24岁的殡葬化妆师
24-year-old/funeral cosmetician
工作时癫痫大发作
suffered a grand mal seizure at work.
- 为什么他能扮Bosley?/- 你想做Bosley?
- Why does he get to be bosley?/- You want to be bosley?
Bosley只是个无性别的信使
Bosley's like the asexual messenger boy.
失去知觉前认为自己被尸体强奸
She had a vision of being raped/by a cadaver before passing out.
抽搐排除了精神方面疾病
Seizure rules out psychiatric illness.
无癫痫史 无脑外伤或吸毒史
No history of epilepsy,head/trauma,or drug use.
3季换了5个天使/Bosley还在继续干呢
Bosley keeps his job while they/replace five angels over three seasons.
可能是颞叶瘤
Could be a tumor to the temporal lobe.
CT扫描是正常的
Not with a normal ct scan.
急诊室医生觉得正常而已
You mean it appeared/normal to the doc in the er.
干得不错 13号
Way to get right back/on that horse,thirteen.
- 刚才那是Amber/- 想得美啊 蛇蝎女
- That was amber./- Nice try,cutthroat bitch.
没听过学13号学得这么不像的
That was the worst thirteen/imitation I've ever heard.
- 殡仪准备室充满了有毒化学剂/- 和尸体
- Funeral home prep rooms are filled with toxic chemicals./- And cadavers.
在那的肯定都死于某原因
Everybody in that place/obviously died from something.
我有问题 假医生是不是就是他?
I have a question.Is he/the one who's not a doctor?
子弹不会传染 但感染 寄生虫...
Bullets aren't contagious.But/infections,parasites...
你说我们中有个假医生 又叫他假货
You said one of us wasn't a/doctor,and you called him a fraud.
他不是医生 继续 Bosley
He's not a doctor.Continue,boz.
- 有可能是性病.../- 为什么还不解雇他?
- Could be an std.../- Why isn't he fired?
哦 画面扭曲
Oh,you're breaking up.
我在过隧道
I'm going into a tunnel.
黑皮肤宗教狂
Dark religious nut.
- 你叫我什么?/- 抱歉
- What did you call me?/- I'm sorry.
你们这星期想怎么称呼?
What do you people want/to be called this week?
Cole
Cole.
这叫人怎么记得住
I'm never gonna remember that.
带上Bosley和其他少数族裔去殡仪馆
Take bosley and the other visible/minority to the funeral home.
剩下的年轻白人 世界是你们的盛宴
The rest of you young,white/people,the world is your oyster.
做核磁共振比对脑电图腰穿和血样涂片
Get an mri with/contrast,eeg,lp,and blood panel.
天使们 小心点
And,angels,be careful.
别以为他是教徒就不会收拾你
Just because he's religious/doesn't mean he won't kick your ass.
- 要打赌么?/- 不
- You want to bet?/- no.
我要你别再混账地对他
I want you to stop/being such a jerk to him.
赌100块
$100.
明智选择 他是个胆小鬼
Smart call.The guy's a wuss.
下一个就炒他
He's gonna be the next one on the train.
定义 "收拾你"
Define "kick your ass."
- 肢体对抗.../- 还是口头对抗?
- Any physical confrontation.../- Or verbal?
- 定义口头对抗/- 超过70分贝的就算
- Define verbal./- Anything over...70 decibels.
你可不能忽然对他友善
And you can't start/suddenly being nice to him.
你这样我只会变本加厉
You realize what/you're encouraging here.
你只会挨揍
Yeah,someone kickin' your ass.
里面的空间比我想象的要小
The space inside is/smaller than I thought.
别担心 Reena
Don't worry,reena.
医生会照顾好你的
The doctors are going to/take good care of you,right?
镇静剂起作用后 感觉会好些
Once the valium kicks/in,you'll feel better.
完了后我们喝点又香又暖的牛奶
And then we'll have some/nice,warm milk when you're done.
- 我宁愿多服点镇静剂/- Reena
- I'd rather have more valium./- Reena.
稍等一下 看看情况
Let's wait just a bit,see how it goes.
尽量别动
Try to lie as still as possible.
老头铁定要刷下去了
I guess father time's a/lock for one of the spots.
13号才是
Thirteen's a lock.
他没行医执照还能呆在这
He doesn't have a medical/license and he's still around.
她害死了那个轮椅男
She killed a guy in a wheelchair.
和他的狗
And his dog.
他才不关心我们的资质
He doesn't care about our qualifications
和想法
or ideas.
他只想找乐子
He just wants to have fun.
她是终极乐趣 因为他猜不透她
And she's the ultimate fun/'cause he can't figure her out.
真是愚蠢的游戏
This game is insane.
那就放弃 输得开心
So quit. Happy to lose the competition.
记在简历上
If it's gonna be on your resume,
自动放弃总比被解雇好些
it's gotta be better/to quit than get fired.
要么放弃要么闭嘴
Either quit or shut up.
事实上跟House做事 被解雇好看些
Actually,with house,getting/fired might look better.
House医生是个危险的自我主义者
Dr. House is a dangerous egomaniac.
这就是我离开他的原因
That's why I left.
我们在如何行医方面意见不一
We had different ideas/on how to practice.
高兴听你这么说
Glad to hear it.
谈谈慈爱医院吧
Tell me about mercy.
老实说我认为Schaffer医生没给我机会
To be honest,I don't think Dr./Schaffer really gave me a chance.
明显没有 你才呆了3星期 发生什么了?
Obviously not.You were there/for three weeks. What happened?
救活了一个病人
Saved a patient's life.
这通常不是解雇的原因啊
That's usually not/grounds for dismissal.
- 你跟她谈过了?/- 是的
- Have you spoken to her?/- Yes.
那为什么还问我?
Then why are you/asking me what happened?
你的简历很出色
You have an excellent resume.
我觉得有必要听听你的说法
I felt I owed it to you to/hear what you had to say.
- 她怎么说?/- 你无视她的指示和医院的程序
- What'd she tell you?/- That you defied her instructions and hospital procedures.
事实就是这样 我没什么好补充的了
That's what happened.Nothing/more I can add to that.
你可以承认做错了
You could tell me that you were wrong.
看来你离开House还是迟了些
Sounds like you didn't leave/house quite soon enough.
尸体和食物都没问题
Cadavers were clean.So is her food.
都是什么狗屁绿色食品
It's all organic unprocessed crap.
应该是防腐剂的问题
It's gotta be the embalming fluid.
- 乙醇对精神有影响.../- Bosley!
- Ethanol can have psychoactive effects.../- Bosley!
跟刚才说话的人说他是白痴
Tell whoever's talking/that he's an idiot.
Bosley 要么骂他白痴
Bosley.Either tell him he's an idiot,
要么证明我是错的
or tell me why I'm wrong.
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
我会接那么简单的病例吗?
You actually think/that I'd take a patient
一个在殡仪馆发病的人
who had a seizure in a funeral home
急诊室难道不会排除防腐剂致病吗?
if the er hadn't already/ruled out embalming fluid?
- 我们不是不该相信.../- 白痴
- I thought we weren't supposed to trust.../- Idiot,
古法语有云 "白痴儿" 专指那些
from the old french,"idiote," meaning
软弱的缺心眼的笨蛋
effeminate,mentally deficient moor.
我在停尸间05年的档案找到这个
I found something in the/mortuary's files from '05.
48岁男性记载着死于肺炎
A 48-year-old male's cause of/death was listed as pneumonia,
但是解剖报告的症状与肺炎不吻合
but the symptoms in the/autopsy report didn't fit.
- 意识障碍 失忆 抑郁/- 疯牛症
- Confusion,memory loss,depression./- Mad cow.
好酷
Very cool.
不 她是个素食者只吃有机蔬菜
No,she's a vegetarian and only/ate organic vegetables at that.
再骂他一次白痴
Tell him he's an idiot again.
病症可以通过脑组织传染
The disease can be/spread by brain tissue.
真酷 活检吧
Which is very cool. Run with it.
只因为答案可能很"酷"
So because the answer might be "cool,"
你想让我们给一个24女人做脑活检?
you want us to do a brain/biopsy on a 24-year-old woman?
不 因为答案很酷
No,because the answer is something cool,
我要你们去给一个48岁死人做脑活检
I want you to do a brain biopsy/on a 48-year-old dead guy.
那人已经葬了
The guy's already been buried.
把他挖出来
We dig him up.
没法庭令我不会去掘墓的
I am not digging up a/body without a court order.
别想成去挖一具尸体
Don't think of it as digging up a body.
想成阻止另外一个人成为尸体
Think of it as keeping/another one from being buried.
我做不了
I can't do it.
我们打算再来些讨论来说明
We gonna have another one of those/ecumenical discussions where I tell you
你的信仰很荒谬然后你再屈服?
that your beliefs are/ridiculous and you totally cave?
我六点就回家
I just gotta be home at 6:00.
安息日
The sabbath.
主工作了六天/跟工会说他要休息一天
The lord works for six days,then/tells the union he needs a rest.
要是我是全能的神
You know,if I was all-powerful,
起码也得休两天吧
it'd take at least two days.
今天星期四
It's thursday.
那肯定是因为孩子了
Well,then it must be the kid.
你裤子上有燕麦粥渍
You have oatmeal on your pants.
- 你装了摄像头?/- 没有 我猜的
- Do you have a camera in here?/- No. I was guessing.
昨天前天他裤子上都有燕麦粥渍
He had oatmeal on his pants/yesterday and the day before.
让你的妻子之一照顾幼崽
Have one of your wives/look after the spawn.
我是单身父亲
I'm a single dad.
那单身妈妈在哪?
Where's the single mom?
我不知道
I have no idea.
有趣
Interesting.
你是说你一时糊涂乱搞了一次
You claim a lapse of judgment,
还是说你的一时糊涂
or you gonna admit/that a lapse in judgment
- 其实是信仰的动摇?/- 他走了
- is a lapse in faith?/- He's gone.
很公平
Fair enough.
家庭优先
Family comes first.
Cuddy医生 我是Amber Volakis/House医生手下一个新人
Dr. Cuddy,i'm amber volakis,one/of Dr. House's new fellows.
性骚扰投诉找人力资源部/压力请假可申请补偿
Sexual harassment claims go through/h.r.Stress-related leaves through worker's comp,
举报犯罪活动
and any accusations/of criminal activities
直接到普林斯顿警局
go directly to the princeton/plainsboro police department.
我想知道今晚门诊还需要人手么
Actually,I was wondering if you needed/any extra help in the clinic tonight.
拍我马屁在House前加不了分
You're not going to score any/points with house by kissing my ass.
明白 但我听说House医生讨厌门诊轮值
Understood.But I hear Dr./House hates clinic duty.
要是他听到流言说我愿意加班
If he were to hear through the grapevine/that I was willing to work overtime,
- 减轻他的负担.../- 我的建议
- take some of it off his hands.../- My advice to you
做House今晚要你做的事
is to do whatever house/wants you to do tonight.
明晚你就可以回来
And then tomorrow/night,you can come back
我会让你值门诊的班的
and I will give you extra clinic duty.
是不是这里所有人都不信任别人?
Does everybody around/here have trust issues?
我不知道House要你做什么/我也不想知道
I don't know what house wants you/to do,and I don't want to know.
但如果你不想做 现在就放弃
But if you really have a/problem with it,quit now.
否则只会越来越糟
It's only gonna get worse.
- 好 轮到谁?/- 不是我
- All right,who's up?/- Not me.
你还没挖过呢
You haven't done any digging yet.
我是外科医生 要是手有什么差错/我就完了
I'm a surgeon.If anything happens/to these hands,I'm screwed.
让Bosley来做 只要他能折衣服...
Let bosley do it.As long as/he can keep folding laundry...
嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh,shh,shh.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
- 我们是不是该逃?/- 要是来的是警察 就逃
- Shouldn't we be running?/- If it's a cop,run.
保安的话 就撂倒他
Security guard,I say we take him down.
抱歉来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
- 你到底去哪了?/- 哦 我迷路了
- Where the hell have you been?/- Oh,I got lost.
我们到了3个小时了
Been here over three hours.
迷得找不到路了
Really lost.
我带了咖啡和面包圈
I brought coffee and donuts.
13号 你在这附近长大的?
So thirteen,you grow up around here?
我们在掘墓 而你想闲聊?
We're digging up a grave,and/you want to chit-chat?
只是想聊聊天 人们都这样啊
I'm just making/conversation.It's what people do.
为什么你要隐藏一切?
Why are you hiding everything?
之所以这么问是因为你把一切藏心底
And I'm asking you that question/because you're hiding everything.
你有不妥
There's something/seriously wrong with you.
我很担心
I'm worried.
不 你没有
No,you're not.
对 我是害怕了/因为我不认为你是个怪物
Fine,but I am freaked,because/I don't think you're a freak.
我认为你是有意这么做的
I think you're doing this on purpose
因为你知道House容易被激起好奇心
because you know house/will be intrigued.
是啊 我在这附近长大
Yeah,I grew up around here.
亲爱的 我到家了
Honey,I'm home.
用撬棍
Get the crowbar.
不够空间使用撬棍
No,there's not enough room to/maneuver a crowbar down here.
上帝保佑
Oh,god help us.
- 什么鬼?/- 什么东西?
- What the hell?/- What is it?
脚踝 他们倒过来埋了
Ankles.They buried the/guy the wrong way around.
医生休息室满是泥巴
The doctor's lounge is covered in mud.
13号和蛇蝎女要打架
Thirteen and cutthroat/bitch had a disagreement,
又找不到啫哩
and the cafeteria was out of jell-o.
还有镐
There were pickaxes.
你要不是让他们去挖尸
Either you had them dig up a body,
就是准备建条铁路
or you're building a railroad.
一点点脑组织而已 不然浪费了
A little tiny piece of/his brain.Seemed a waste.
- 反正他不会再用了/- 这就是你的辩护?
- He wasn't using it anymore./- That's your defense?
"我们就这样肢解了他"?
"we just dismembered him"?
他们在查克雅氏病病原
They're looking for creutzfeldt-jakob.
有结果了?
You get the results yet?
我的气息对你有诱惑力吗?
Does my breath smell baited to you?
有
Yes.
有消息通知我
Let me know when you hear anything.
收拾干净你的烂摊子
And get that mess in the/shower area cleaned up.
刚好有个人能干这活
I know just the guy.
有多少个同意掘墓?
How many of them agreed/to dig up a grave?
6个
Six.
别担心 剩下那个不是因为原则而不同意
But don't worry,the one who/didn't didn't stand on principle.
只是要换尿片而已
He just had a diaper to change.
我实在想不出要淘汰谁了
I really think there are no/bad choices in this group.
你们进来时不擦脚吗?
You guys don't wipe your feet/when you come in the house?
医生休息室 赶紧去
Doctor's lounge.Let's go.
为什么是我?
Why me?
我不能叫黑人或女人去做啊
I can't ask the black guy or/one of the chicks to do it,
这样太不善解人意了
that would be insensitive.
你又不能让Bosley做
And you can't ask bosley
因为这样你就请了非医生做闲事了
because that'd look like you only hired/the non-doctor to do non-doctor stuff.
拖延时间 你还是得去清洁
You keep stalling,you're/still gonna clean up,
到时候可没有拖把了
but I won't let you have the mop.
克雅氏病阴性
Sample came back negative/for creutzfeldt-jakob.
这次讨论持续不久啊
Well,that discussion didn't last long.
我想不出还有别的了
I just don't know what else there is.
我们有个想法
We had an idea.
却是错的
It was wrong.
那我们可以回家了
Well,we can go home.
我们不知道她得了什么病
I mean,we have no idea/what's wrong with her.
那么有可能是良性的
Which means it could/be completely benign.
或者运气不好的话会害死她
Or,on the off chance/that it'skillingher,
我们可以从头再来
we could take it again from the top.
你们已经全验过了
You've already done everything.
我们可能遗漏了些东西
We may have missed something.
我只想回家 我现在没事了
I just want to go/home.I'm sure I'm fine now.
Reena 医生懂得多
Reena,the doctors know best.
你之前的症状很严重 抽搐...
You had some serious/symptoms.The seizure...
要是我又发作了/我马上回来 行吗?
If I have another one,i'll/come right back,okay?
要是开车的时候发作...
If you have it while you're driving...
你可以载我 让我轻松点
You can drive me.Make/sure I take it easy.
谁可以载你?
Who can?
我妈啊
My mother.
- 你妈在这?/- 你在说什么?她就在那
- Your mother's here?/- What are you talking about?She's right there.
所有体液都采样了 也看过脑子了
You sampled every bodily/fluid,peeked in her brain,
冒犯了尸体 挖出了死尸
violated a cadaver's/privacy,dug up a body,
却错过了一个事实
but missed the fact
她仍然看到不存在的东西
she was still seeing/things that weren't there.
神经症状更严重了
Neurological symptoms are getting worse.
要是你们这些天使-笨蛋/能知道为什么就好了
It'd be nice if one of you/angels、morons had a clue why.
我们问过病史了/她从没提过见到听到不寻常的东西
We did a full history.She never mentioned/seeing or hearing anything unusual.
要是她什么都没说
Oh,well,as long as she/never said anything.
那你又怎么知道?/跟脊髓液一样?
How were you to know?Same/thing with the spinal fluid?
她说没事?
She tell you that was fine?
化验都是正常的
The labs were all clear.
那么我们所有检查都做一次
Then either we're about to/meet the alpha and omega,
否则一定会错过什么
or you missed something.
- 我们错过了新症状/- 不是什么新症状
- We missed the new symptom./- It's not a new symptom.
我们一直都知道她有幻觉
We always knew she had hallucinations.
见到死去的母亲是幻觉
Seeing her dead/mother's a hallucination.
以为母亲没死 这是妄想症
Not knowing she's dead is a delusion.
保持下去 你将成为未来的青春偶像
You keep this up,you're gonna have/to start wearing sexier clothes.
一氧化碳也可能引起妄想
Uh,carbon monoxide could/also cause delusions.
- 许多所谓的鬼屋.../- 无头痛 无心跳过速
- A lot of haunted houses.../- There's no headache.No tachycardia.
你上医学院的时候好像没学这些
I guess they didn't cover/that atyourmedical school.
会不会是遗传病?
What about a hereditary connection?
她24岁 她母亲死的时候才25岁
She's 24.Her mother/died when she was 25.
20年前死在乌克兰/不可能拿到病历
In ukraine,20 years ago.Good/luck trying to get those records.
我们重建一份病历
We start new records.
查查与这些症状相符的遗传病
Test for every hereditary/disease that fits the symptoms.
至少有40种线粒体疾病/还有几百种别的...
There are at least 40 different mitochondrial/disorders,another couple hundred...
从淀粉样变性病开始/一直查到...
Start with amyloidosis,keep/going until you reach...
词表的尾页
Zamyloidosis.
现在你想查什么?
Now what are you testing for?
是不是应该问哪些不查?
Or should I ask what/you're not testing for?
要是你还记得你妈是怎么死的
Well,we could narrow it down
那我们或许能把范围缩小点
if you could rember what/your mother died from.
我妈没死 她就坐在这
My mother is not dead.She's/sitting right there.
- 你以为我在骗你们?/- 算了吧.
- Do you think we're lying to you?/- Leave it alone.
让她承认她母亲已经去世了/不会让她好过
Convincing her that her mother's/dead isn't gonna make her better,
只会让她痛苦
just miserable.
你失去了母亲?
You lose your mother?
你以为我们在和你玩什么花样?
Do you think we're trying to trick you?
我们干嘛要那样呢?
Why would we do that?
因为你们是坏人
Because you're mean.
你们很不称职
And you're not good at your job.
Reena 算了 你好没礼貌
Reena,stop.You're being cruel.
他们在浪费时间...
They're wasting time...
跟轮椅上的那个家伙说的一样
Doing exactly what the guy in/the wheelchair said they'd do.
- 这有个坐轮椅的人?/- 你知道我说的是谁
- A guy in a wheelchair was here?/- You know who I'm talking about.
我住进这病房 他就一直在这里
He's been hanging around/ever since they brought me in
不停抱怨你们这些人多无能
complaing about how/incompetent everyone is.
还说你们害死了他的狗
Said you killed his dog.
- 理由说不通/- 我不感兴趣
- It doesn't make any sense./- I'm not interested.
要是不感兴趣 你就不会来了
If you weren't interested,you/wouldn't be here.
我以为只是社会交往
I thought it was social.
你才不是 你做什么都有目的
No,you didn't.You always/think there's an agenda.
- 所以我辞职了/- 所以你厉害
- That's why I left./- That's why you're good.
- 你需要工作/- 我会找份工作
- You need a job./- I'll find a job.
- 我需要有人能理解house/- 他们会学会
- And I need someone that understands house./- They'll learn.
- 我需要有人能控制house/- 切
- I need someone that can control house./- ha.
那你继续找 估计要找一阵子
Keep looking.Might take awhile.
我会把组里每人的薪水砍掉15%,/然后算到你头上
I'll cut the salary of everyone/else on the team 15%,give it to you.
那会比你在其他地方拿的工资多得多
That's more than you'll/get anywhere else.
House 他怎么看?
What does house say about this?
在这组里他一直很敬重你
You're the one person on the/team that he always respected.
这家餐馆离你有20分钟路程
This restaurant is 20/minutes out of your way.
离我半个多小时
Half an hour out of mine.
你选这个地方是怕被House撞见
You picked it to make sure/house didn't drop in on us.
我做的决定 和他无关
It's my decision,not his.
把我往那里一丢 躲回办公室/让我自己去跟House解释?
And you tell him that,then run back to/your office while I get to deal with him.
我离开是有原因的/这种原因一直没有改变
I left for a reason,and/that reason hasn't changed.
那么...有什么消息?
So... What's the news?
目前什么都没查到
Everything's negative so far.
为什么不等全查完再来汇报?
Yes. Why wait to finish/before reporting to me?
我还有事在身 你也知道
I have things to do,you know.
- 她又看见另外的人了/- 这不是新闻
- She's seeing someone else./- That's not news.
这是旧闻
That's olds.
他妈的
Damn it.
老天干嘛把人体设计成这样?
Why did god design the/human body this way?
- 看到一个坐轮椅的人/- 在医院里
- A guy in a wheelchair./- In a hospital.
一个轮椅男就让你神经过敏啦
It's enough to give/you the heebie-jeebies.
还有只狗 她看到的是Stark
He had adog.She's seeing stark.
我们的上一个病人
Our last patient.
要是Stark有鬼魂/他不会缠着病人
Well,if it's stark,he/wouldn't be haunting a patient,
他会直接找杀死他的医生
he'd be haunting the/doctor who killed him.
可能她听到有人谈论这事...
She probably just overheard/someone talking about it...
可能?
Probably?
意思是说她看见鬼魂也是一种可能?
You think there's a possibility/that the alternative is true?
- 不是/- 那走吧
- no./- Then go away.
我们在浪费时间 跑了32个胶板/可能还要跑100多个
We're wasting time.We ran 32/gels.We could run 100 more.
如果不知道她妈怎么死的...
Without knowing how her mother died...
那你只能把这100多个跑完
You're gonna have to run 100 more.
刚才那话只说给有良心的人听
And by you,of course,i'm/only referring to the people
愿意为了救人而留下加班的人
who care enough about human/life to put in a full day.
要不要合伙拼车?
You want to carpool?
你认为我应该做何反应?
how do you expect me to/respond to this stuff?
就是这种反应
Exactly like you just did.
我有个想法 也许你可以帮我
I have a theory.Maybe/you can help me out.
黑人摩门教徒是受虐狂
Black mormon means masochist.
喜欢玩刺激
Means kinky.
造那小杂种的过程/一定是伤痕累累吧?
I'm thinking that someone got/hurt making the bastard.Am I right?
别把我儿子扯进来
You leave my son out of this.
我没提你儿子虚伪 我是说你
I wasn't referring to your kid's/hypocrisy.I was referring to yours.
我们干嘛不直接问她/母亲是怎么死的?
Why don't we just ask/her how she died,hm?
她不会说的
Because she won't tell us.
她一直以为她妈还活着
She thinks her mother's still alive.
不是问病人 是直接问她母亲
I don't mean ask the/patient,I mean ask her mother.
酷
Cool.
走
Come on.
你的话什么意思?
What the hell does that mean?
你们这帮老家伙有暗语吗?
You guys talking your own language now?
很抱歉 下次我会多加一些辅助手势
I'm sorry.I'll try to include/some visual aids next time.
怎么啦?
Now what?
我是House医生
I'm Dr. House.
- 你妈在附近吗?/- 干嘛要告诉你?
- Is your mom around?/- Why should I tell you?
我一说出来你们就会说我撒谎 说我疯狂
You're just going to tell/me i'm lying or crazy.
我不会的
Not gonna do that.
我很想知道她会说什么
I really need to know/what she has to say.
你想干嘛?
What do you want?
- 你小的时候 她.../- 不 不是你 是他.
- When you were young,was she.../- No,not you. Him.
- 坐轮椅的那位?/- 不是
- The man in the wheelchair?/- no.
他上年纪了
He's old.
事实上 和你比较像
Actually,looks like you.
不错 那是house爷爷
Yeah,that's grandpa house.
叫他找个固话再打过来
Tell him to call back on a land line.
信号真差
Terrible reception in here.
你母亲是否很痛?
How much pain was your mom in?
- 我是Walter/- 他自称Walter
- It's walter./- He says his name is walter.
你有事吗?
Can I help you?
我的病人在和我的祖父Walt聊天
My patient's talking to my grandpa walt.
你有位叫Walt的祖父?
You have a grandpa walt?
没有
no.
这正证实了我的猜想/她并没有看到什么死后的灵魂
Which is what made me suspect that maybe/she's not actually seeing into the afterlife.
你怎么突然对死后的灵魂着了魔
What is this sudden/obsession with the afterlife?
我关注的是在世的
Only obsession is with the idiots/in the right-here-and-now life
相信灵魂不灭的白痴
who think there's an afterlife.
那你是希望我去...
And you want me to...
什么都不需要/我只是想找个地方躲会
Nothing. Just need a place/to hang low for awhile.
假装我被她吓到了
I'm pretending to be spooked.
因为...
Because...
因为-如果那个濒临脑死亡的病人/觉得我相信了她
Because if my soon-to-be brain-dead/patient thinks that I believe her,
也许她会允许我和她妈妈的灵魂聊聊
maybe she'll let me chat/with her mother's ghost.
和那个不存在的妈妈聊?
The one you don't believe exists.
没错 那灵魂是她的幻觉/也就是妄想症的一种体现
Exactly. The ghost is a hallucination,/ which is the result of a delusion
基本可以推断是遗传类疾病
which most likely is the/result of a hereditary disease
也就是她四岁时 她母亲的死因
that her mother died from/when the patient was four.
而你认为你可以通过和她的幻觉沟通
And you think you can tap/into her subconscious memory
从而找到深藏在她记忆下的潜意识
by tapping into her hallucination.
她也许不清楚她母亲的死因
She might not know what/caused her mother's death,
但是她应记得她母亲死前的一些症状
but she will know how/she acted before she died.
你很佩服自己是吧
You're quite impressed with/yourself right now, aren't you?
谁不会呢
Who wouldn't be?
好了 差不多是时候了
Well,that should be long enough.
马上回来
Back in a flash.
不用急
Take your time.
我祖父还在吗
Is my grandfather still here?
不
no.
应该等会就回来了
He should be right back.
他出去买些热牛奶
He just went to get some warm milk.
那你母亲还在吧
But your mom's still here, right?
当然
Yes,of course.
我知道她现在很健康/不过在你4,5岁的时候 她是不是病了
I know she's fine now, but when/you were 4 or 5,she got sick.
没有
no.
你确定?
You sure?
她有没有感到疼痛
She wasn't in any pain?
我没觉得哪里痛
I wasn't in pain.
她只是经常疲劳
She was just tired.
有些时候她会整日卧床
And sometimes she would/stay in bed all day.
她曾跌倒过吗
Did she ever fall down?
当然
Of course.
谁都会偶尔跌倒
Everyone falls down once in awhile.
有时 没那么频繁
Sometimes.Not that often.
大约多久一次
How often?
也许比偶尔多一些
Maybe it was actually/more than once in awhile.
记得在洗手间那次吗
Remember that time in the bathroom?
有那么几次吧
A few times.
曾有一次她的头撞到了盥洗池上
Once she hit her head/on the bathroom sink.
地板上都全都是血
There was blood all over the floor.
连我套衫上都是
I got it on my sweater.
他们把她送走了
They took her away.
对 把她送去医院治疗
To the place where the/doctor made her better.
在她摔倒之前/你有留意她的手脚活动吗
But before that, what/about her arms and legs?
是否有时走路有点滑稽
Did she ever walk funny?
有些勾背
Like sort of bent over?
我一直以为/那是小时候在农场干活累出来的
I thought that was from/growing up on the farm.
她的手是什么状况
What about her hands?
是不是做针线很困难
She ever have any difficulty sewing,
钉扣子困难?
buttoning a shirt?
没有
no.
不过有时 我的手会不由自主的颤抖
But sometimes, my hands would,um,shiver.
就好像我冻着了那样
Like I was cold.
但我并不觉的冷
But I wasn't.
我一直不太明白
I never quite understood.
她过去经常颤抖/就好像感冒了那样
She used to get the/shivers like she was cold.
给她服用 左旋多巴和溴麦角环肽
Start her on l-dopa and bromocriptine.
只不过是帕金森综合症而已
It's just parkinson's.
Cole.
你们病人的情况怎么样
How's it going with your patient?
仍然"看"得到一些东西
Still seeing stuff.
我听说House把你唾弃的一文不值
I hear house is treating you like crap.
他对谁都态度恶劣
He treats everyone badly.
是 但我听说对你更是多加关照
Yeah,but I heard you're special.
我倒还能承受
Oh,I can handle it.
也许你不该逆来顺受
Maybe you shouldn't.
你越容忍他 他越整治你
He's gonna walk all/over you if you let him.
你还是没说我应该怎么办
That says nothing about me, just him.
House只会对勇于和他唱反调的人给与尊重
House respects people/who aren't afraid of him.
当面对峙
Get in his face.
吼两句也无妨
Yell if you have to.
我不需要得到他的尊重
I don't need his respect.
你会的 如果你想得到这份工作的话
You do if you want the job.
多谢指点
Thanks for the advice.
你尽量别动
You have to hold still!
我已经在尽力了!
I'm trying!
该死的! 按牢她!
Damn! Hold her down!
不! 不要!
No! Stop it!
让我来!
Let me do it!
抓牢她!
Hold her down!
不! 不! 不!
No! No! No!
不
no
Irene.
Irene?
你扎了我
You stabbed me.
你只是做了个恶梦 那都不是真的
You were having a nightmare.Wasn't real.
我的手臂在流血
My arm is bleeding.
不用担心 你的手臂没...
No,it's okay now.Your arm's not...
帕金森综合症无法解释她的皮肤损伤
Lesions aren't explained by parkinson's.
有什么解释?
Any theories?
鬼缠舌?
A ghost got your tongue?
我没事
I'm fine.
会不会是脉管炎
What about vasculitis?
磁共振显示没有脑局部缺血现象
Mri didn't indicate/any cerebral ischemia.
但她有局部肌无力和尿潴留症状
But she has shown some focal/weakness,urinary retention.
这都不是关键的症状
Yes,those are her big mystery symptoms.
最重要的幻觉/却是脉管炎无法解释的
Not the hallucinations that/vasculitis doesn't explain.
视网膜脉管炎可以解释
Unless it's retinal vasculitis.
House 这家伙也许真的很聪明/我敢肯定他还是个优秀的酒肉哥们
House,this guy may be smart,and I'm/sure he's great to share a beer with.
但如果他不知道/视觉病症是神经系统上的问题
But if he doesn't know that visual/symptoms are an electrical issue,
而不是血管上的/这是两个完全分离的系统
not vascular,two separate systems...
这就好比银行和电力公司
So are the banks and the power grid.
如果我不去银行交费/就会被掐断电源
But if I don't pay my/bills,my lights go out.
脉管炎限制了神经血流供应
Vasculitis restricts/blood flow to nerves,
扰乱神经电信号
messes with electrical function.
拿急性间歇卟啉症来解释倒更贴切些
Acute intermittent/porphyria's a better fit.
如果你关于卟啉症的诊断有误/错误的药物足以废了她的肾脏
If you're wrong about porphyria,the/treatment could box her kidneys.
治疗脉管炎的用药是皮质类固醇
Vasculitis is treated/with corticosteriods.
危害较小
Relatively harmless.
开始对她使用类固醇
Start her on the steroids.
House 这...
House,this gu...
并同时检验血管炎和卟啉症两项/省得他再发牢骚
And test for both so he'll stop whing.
博爱的人/前半个小时里我找你麻烦了吗
Big love, have I humiliated/you in the last half hour?
没有
no.
去查阅下你的电子信件
Check your email.
怎么样
How's it going?
很不错
Great.
要想激得他发脾气/恐怕只能当众扒他裤子了
The only way he could turn any more/cheeks is by pulling down his pants.
他不是胆小鬼
He's not a wuss.
你的力气还不够扒他...
It takes a lot more strength...
我们赌的可不是他的力气
Hey,we didn't bet on how strong he was.
那么你打算解雇他 赢下100块/只因为他是个讲究原则的人?
So you're gonna collect $100 and/fire him because he has principles?
你的目的到底是什么
What's your agenda here?
很明显你并不在乎输掉那100块
Obviously don't care about the $100.
他是一个聪明正派的...
He's a decent, smart...
你不在意团队怎样
You don't care about the team.
Wilson有没有说过/你这种问话又不想听回答的态度让他很烦
Does it annoy wilson when you ask/questions and ignore the answers?
烦透了
Very much.
你只在乎我聘用了谁 又解雇了谁
You only care about who/I hire and who I fire,
因为你怀念帮我处理信件的时光了
'cause you miss going through my mail.
你就是忍不住想控制我
You can't stop controlling me.
没人能控制你
No one controls you.
- 想回来工作?/- 不
- Want your job back?/- no.
太糟了 想回来也不要你
Too bad.You can't have it.
这些由她来付
She'll take care of this.
你可以从欠我的100块中扣掉
You can take it out of the/$100 you're gonna owe me.
五年前的一个会议上/我曾见过House一面
I met house at a conference/about five years ago.
他确实是个人物
He's quite a character.
是 他是的
Yes,he is.
他的医学思维/可能是我们这个时代最棒的
Probably one of the best/medical minds of our generation.
我赞同/我从他那里学到了很多
I agree. I learned/an awful lot from him.
我相信是的
I'll bet you did.
这里写着你刚刚在慈爱医院工作过
I see here,just did a/stint at mercy. Great.
07年至今
It says here "'07 to present."
你在那呆了多久
How long were you there?
大约一个月
About a month.
Schaffer医生十分优秀/但我不太适应那里
Dr. Schaffer was great, but/just wasn't the right fit.
等一下 Schaffer医生的那个淋巴瘤病人?
Wait,was that you with Dr./Schaffer and the lymphoma patient?
是的 情况比较复杂
It was,um,it was a tough situation.
也许我本来可以做的更好一些
I probably could've handled it better.
不是这个意思/教训一下Schaffer医生是应该的
No. Dr. Schaffer's got/a stick up her rear.
你做的很好
Good for you.
是什么让你这么肯定是淋巴癌
What made you so sure it was lymphoma?
在其中一项她的试验报告中/她的乳酸水准偏高
There was an unusual lactic/acid level in one of her labs.
而我几个月前刚好有一个类似的诊断经历
I had a similar case a few months ago.
太妙了
Beautiful.
老天 我真希望我能拥有你的魄力
God,I wish I had your stones.
我的魄力可以为你所用
Well,my stones areon the market.
说真的 我希望拥有你的胆识
No,I mean,seriously, I/wish I had your stones.
那我就可以帮你说服董事们聘用你
Then I could cram you down/the board of directors.
但是我没有
But I don't.
很抱歉
I'm sorry,man.
祝你好运
Good luck.
当你的视网膜收到了图象/它们会向大脑输送电信号
When your retina sees something,they/send electrical signals to your brain.
而这些镜片会捕捉到那些信号
These lenses will pick up those signals.
如果信号不正常
If the signals are misfiring,
说明无照行医的老头子比我们更聪明
it'll confirm that an old man without a/medical license is smarter than all of us.
也就是说你的幻觉是由于...
That your hallucinations/were caused by...
这不是幻觉
They're not hallucinations.
告诉她  妈妈
Tell her,mom.
甜心 他们是医生
Honey,they're doctors.
他们一定很清楚他们在做什么
They must know what they're doing.
如果他们称职 怎么会害死那人的狗
If they know what they're doing,how'd/they kill that poor man's dog?
别告诉我 你一点也没被吓到
Come on,this has got to be/freaking you out a little bit.
谢谢你的关心
I appreciate your concern.
这没什么丢脸的
There's nothing to be ashamed of here.
如果被你害死的男人的灵魂没有干扰到你
If the ghost of a man you killed/doesn't screw with your head,
那你才真的出了问题
there's something wrong with your head.
看到了吗  我也被吓到了
See,that freaks me out.
一定是有人丢在这里的
Someone must've left it in here.
是是 这合情合理
Oh,absolutely.That makes sense.
某条狗在这里检查检查眼睛之后/忘记把它的项链戴回去了
The dog was in here getting his eyes/checkedand forgot to put his jewelry back on.
这样没用
This isn't working.
就像他说的那样/你们是在让我病上加病而已
You're just making me/sicker like he said you...
出了什么事
What's wrong?
我的胃很痛
My stomach,it hurts.
- 眼科实验室有情况/- 向前探 Irene
- Code in the eye lab./- Lean forward,irene.
你要吸气
You're gonna aspirate.
我做不到 很痛
I can't. It hurts.
你为什么不帮帮我?
Why won't you help me?
脾脏烂到裂开
Spleen's ripe to bursting.
你们还以为是脉管炎?
You guys thought it was vasculitis?
你以前是在House的团队里对吗
You used to be on house's team,right?
是的
Yeah.
这里有大量的出血 递海绵来
There's a lot of blood in here. Sponge.
有什么好的建议吗
You got any advice for me?
没
Nope.
你总是对他的凌辱逆来顺受吗
Did you always put up with his crap?
没错
Yup.
纵容他是错的吗
Was it a mistake?
跟这个没关系
It was irrelevant.
可他解雇了你
He fired you.
不管是什么原因
He'll fire you either way...
他最终都会解雇你
Eventually.
Cameron医生告诉我说...
Dr. Cameron told me...
别说 别说了
No,no,no.
怎么
Why not?
因为...
'cause...
House正在看着呢
House is watching.
不是暗喻 朝上看
Not a metaphor.Look up.
你们是要闲扯还是要止血?
You guys gonna shoot the breeze or you/gonna do something about all that bleeding?
内出血不是来自脾脏
That's not coming from the spleen.
是肝脏
It's the liver.
坏死了
It's necrotic.
内部坏死正在消耗她的生命
She's dying from the inside out.
肿大的脾脏和肝功能丧失/是典型的自身免疫性胰腺炎
Enlarged spleen and liver/failure are classic a.i.p.
是卟啉症 病情在迅速扩张
It's porphyria and it's moving fast.
胆色素原测试阴性
Pbgs were negative...
如果你读过那报告
If you read the report.
只有发病中的胆色素原测试/才能下定论
Pbg tests are only conclusive/if done during an attack,
如果你是个真正的医生/你就会了解
which you would know if/you were a real doctor.
真是太精彩了
That is just great.
- 什么?/- 你指的谁?
- What is?/- Which one of us is?
你们两个  一起
Both of you.Together.
激情辩论
Fighting.
奋力证明对方是错的
Passionate to prove the other one wrong.
对病人毫不关心
Couldn't care less about the patient,
反正也救不活
but it all works out the same.
我讨厌13号
I hate thirteen.
光讨厌没有用
Not as productively.
继续
Continue.
仍有可能是血管方面的问题
It could still be vascular.
脉管炎已经被否决
Vasculitis is off the board.
类固醇治疗没起任何作用
Steroid treatment didn't help.
血管方面的疾病并不只有脉管炎一种
Vascular isn't just vasculitis.
有什么东西阻止了她的/肝脏和脾脏的血液供给
Something's gotta be cutting off the/blood supply to her liver and spleen.
去做一个内脏血管造影
Do a visceral angiogram.
这是开玩笑吧
This is a joke,right?
不可能次次都是他对
He can't be right every single time.
你授意他这么说/借他的口让我们难堪
You're feeding him your/ideas just to embarrass us.
如果我想让你难堪/我会让你去拖医生休息室的地板
If I wanted to embarrass you, i'd/have you mop up the doctor's lounge.
天父啊
Heavenly father,
我祈求你把圣灵赐给
I pray thee that thou shalt/give the holy ghost unto all them
那些信你的人
that shall believe in their words.
Irene.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我要摸
I need to touch it.
Irene 把你的手放下
Irene,put your hand down.
不 把它给我
No,give it to me!
我想要
I want it!
快给我!
Give it to me!
血管造影的结果如何
What'd the angio say?
做不成 她一直在摸我
We couldn't finish.She/started groping me.
你就不能为了试验献身/让她到达二垒?
You couldn't let her get to second/base just to get the test done?
我觉得那已经到三垒了
I think that's third base.
她一直在抽筋 发狂/并且过量的唾液分泌
She was convulsing,delirious,/and hyper-salivating.
用镇静剂才让她安静
We had to knock her out with lorazepam.
这肯定不是血管类疾病
Well,it's definitely not vascular.
你想要我们怎么做
What do you want us to do?
问题是如果是Joseph Smith会怎么做?/ (摩门教创始人)
Question is what would joseph smith do?
这种时候不是...
This isn't the time for...
他会驱除魔鬼?
Casting out the demons?
病人并没有被魔鬼附身/她就快死了
The patient's not possessed.she's dying.
你可以明天再继续嘲弄我
you can mock me tomorrow.
你相信所有的答案都写在你的教义里
you believe that the/book has all the answers.
指的是道德上的/不是科学方面的
to morality. Not science.
但那信仰却和科学背道而驰
but the book is/inconsistent with science.
你知道有多少癫痫病人/因被当成魔鬼附身而受到毒打?
you know how many epileptics were/tortured because they were possessed?
多少年轻的巫师吃了毒蘑菇致死?
how many teenage witches were stoned/to death 'cause they took mushrooms?
闭嘴!
just shut up already!
我们的病人正濒临死亡!
we got a patient dying!
你要不就去开个驱魔的药方来/要不就给我承认Smith是个好色的骗子
either got to prescribe an exorcism or/admit to me that smith was a horny fraud.
我知道她患得什么病了
I know what she has.
你就不能提前10 秒钟说出来?
you couldn't have spoken/up ten seconds ago?
害我输掉100块
you could have saved me 100 bucks.
不只是蘑菇才会让人欲仙欲死
mushrooms weren't the only thing/that got people stoned to death.
曼陀罗 颠茄 曼德拉草/和发霉的面包
jimson weed,belladonna,/mandrake root,and moldy bread.
是麦角中毒
it's ergot poisoning.
潮湿的谷物
you'd need damp grain that had been...
完全没经过加工处理的
completely unprocessed/and untreated like
就像她吃的有机黑面包里含有的那种
what's in that organic rye/bread she's been eating.
我该回家了吗?
should I be going home?
6点了吗?
is it 6:00?
溴麦角环肽让她病情加重/就是这个原因...
it's why she got worse/on the bromocriptine...
它是麦角的一种衍生物
it's an ergot derivative.
这是50多年来的首例
there hasn't been a case in 50 years.
她不断的要喝牛奶
she kept asking for milk.
乳制品可消解麦角的毒性作用
dairy products counteract the effects.
你以为她明白自己的病情/并加以治疗吗？
you think she knew what/she had and was treating it?
强烈的需求来自于实际的需要
cravings based on actual needs.
不过是很寻常的进化本能而已
it's a fairly common/evolutionary development.
你可以接受基于进化论的答案吗?
you okay with an answer/based on evolution?
可以
yeah.
虚伪
hypocrite.
这是他们用来做迷幻药的东西
it's the stuff they make lsd from.
对你的治疗应该能...
the treatment you're on should...
这么说我是...嗨了一下？
so I've just been... Tripping?
这可以解释幻觉/抽搐和妄想等症状
it explains the hallucinations,/seizures,delusions.
导致血管收缩 进而坏死
constricts the blood vessels,/which explains the necrosis.
她不在这?
she's not here?
抱歉 不在
i'm sorry. No.
既然你愿意接受这个回答
the fact that you're even/willing to accept that answer
表明药物开始生效了
means the medicine is starting to work.
可你会活下去的
but you'll live.
你真美 Reena
you're beautiful,reena.
你也是 妈妈
you too,mama.
我会想你的
i'm going to Miss you.
妈妈
ma.
如你所知 你们一共有7个人..
as you know, there/are seven of you and...
可只有6朵玫瑰
only six roses.
是牡丹
those are peonies.
不过我肯定它们跟玫瑰同科的
but I'm sure they're/part of the rose family.
实际上我很吃惊会有7个人
actually,I'm surprised/there are seven of you.
你揍了你老板然后还等在这?
you punch your boss and stick around?
闭嘴 把花给我
give me the flower and shut up.
别太过火了
don't overdo it.
我很乐意把所有人都留下来
now I would love to keep all of you.
但还没乐意到真替你们去争取
but not enough to do anything about it.
所以根据我的仲裁计划
so according to my arbitrary schedule,
你们中有一个人必须走
one of you has to go.
你不是开玩笑吧
you're kidding.
我找出了答案
I came up with the answer.
我去盗墓 我...
I robbed a grave. I...
在眼科室放了个狗圈/好扰乱我的心神
planted a dog collar in the procedure/room just to screw with my head.
不 我从没...
no,I never...
你觉得不是她干的?
you don't believe she did it?
我很肯定是她干的
i'm sure she did it.
所以她得到了一朵花
that's why she's getting the flower.
真美
it was beautiful.
她不过是弄巧成拙
she just overreached.
她得逞了
she got into your head.
没
no.
她吓着你了
she owned you.
心理暗示有一套
planting the idea was good.
后来的造势也不错
letting it fester was good.
放置狗圈就太蠢了
leaving the collar was stupid.
众所周知 鬼魂不会丢三落四
well known fact, ghosts don't/leave things lying around.
这么说轮到我走了?
so am I gone then?
噢 我的天哪
oh,my goodness.
我完全忘了你们俩了
I had totally forgotten about you two.
干的不错
well played.
抱歉 Henry
sorry,henry.
你给我们带来不少笑料
we had some giggles.
他说的所有话你都赞同
you agreed with everything he said.
你们俩几乎心意相通
you finished each other's sentences.
这就是我出局的原因
that's why I gotta go.
自己明白的事不用别人再指出来了
don't need someone to tell you/what you're already thinking.
有趣 我正准备这么说
funny,I was gonna say that.
如果你想打发时间...
if you want to hang out...
是啊 我明白
yeah,I know.
恩 给Wilson打电话
um,call wilson.
其他人 明天8点见
rest of you, 8:00 tomorrow.
现金就好
cash will be fine.
我猜你跟人上床之后都这么说
I bet you say that to all the guys.
拿走你罪恶的钱
take your blood money.
接下来你要保护谁?
who are you gonna protect next?
告诉你 就不管用了
if I told you, it wouldn't work.
我重新考虑了一下
I've rethought some things.
洗耳恭听
glad to hear it.
如果满足以下条件 我就准备回来
i'm prepared to come back/on a number of conditions.
在你承诺加薪的基础上 再加5%
I want the raise you/promised, plus five percent.
我要单独的办公室和一名个人助理
I want my own office/and a personal assistant.
也不算漫天开价
it's not unreasonable.
我打算...一条也不答应
I will give you...none of those.
你可以回来 薪水不变
you can come back at/your original salary.
什么意思?
what's going on?
你压根没有重新考虑/你不过是陷入困境了
you haven't rethought anything./you've just been blackballed.
现在你也成了‘House’型的了
you're "house light" now.
只有雇用‘经典House’的老板/才肯接受你
the only administrator that will touch/you is the one who hired "house classic."
好在她会假装不是/在帮你的忙
good news is, she'll pretend/she's not doing you a favor.
我星期一能来上班
I can start monday.